megadumpload.com 2018-05-25

# Privacy Policy for Megadumpload

_The owners of the Megadumpload website are committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to the site._

The owners of the Megadumpload website care abour protecting the privacy of all visitors to the website, and do not collect any personally identifiable information about such visitors and website users without their express permission.

Some information about visitors' web browsers, operating systems and location may be collected through normal operation of the website and stored in cookies. None of the information collected will ever be used to personally identify any user of the site except where required by law. In addition, no information about users of the Megadumpload website will ever be sold, rented, shared or given to any third party for the purposes of spam, unsolicited marketing or other unauthorized commercial activity.

No information is deliberately collected by the Megadumpload website or its owners about persons under the age of 13 years. Concerned parents of people under the age of 13 may contact the owners of the Megadumpload website to have any such information removed.

The Megadumpload website contains links to third party websites, and use of those third party websites may be subject to their own Privacy Policy. Users are advised to read the Privacy Policy of any third party website before using any services or products featured on any such website. Use of the Amazon website is subject to the Privacy Policy as displayed on that website, and a link to the Privacy Policy for that website can be found on the main page of that website.

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be updated on this website. Last updated 3 March, 2018.
